[{"question": "Which of the following commands will create a list?", "options": ["A. list1 = list()", "B. list1 = []", "C. list1 = list([1, 2, 3])", "D. all of the mentioned"], "answer": "D. all of the mentioned"}, {"question": "What is the output when we execute list(\u201chello\u201d)?", "options": ["A. [\u2018h\u2019, \u2018e\u2019, \u2018l\u2019, \u2018l\u2019, \u2018o\u2019]", "B. [\u2018hello\u2019]", "C. [\u2018llo\u2019]", "D. [\u2018olleh\u2019]"], "answer": "A. [\u2018h\u2019, \u2018e\u2019, \u2018l\u2019, \u2018l\u2019, \u2018o\u2019]"}, {"question": "Suppose listExample is [\u2018h\u2019,\u2019e\u2019,\u2019l\u2019,\u2019l\u2019,\u2019o\u2019], what is len(listExample)?", "options": ["A. 5", "B. 4", "C. None", "D. Error"], "answer": "A. 5"}, {"question": "Suppose list1 is [2445,133,12454,123], what is max(list1)?", "options": ["A. 2445", "B. 133", "C. 12454", "D. 123"], "answer": "C. 12454"}, {"question": "Suppose list1 is [3, 5, 25, 1, 3], what is min(list1)?", "options": ["A. 3", "B. 5", "C. 25", "D. 1"], "answer": "D. 1"}, {"question": "Suppose list1 is [1, 5, 9], what is sum(list1)?", "options": ["A. 1", "B. 9", "C. 15", "D. Error"], "answer": "C. 15"}, {"question": "To shuffle the list(say list1) what function do we use?", "options": ["A. list1.shuffle()", "B. shuffle(list1)", "C. random.shuffle(list1)", "D. random.shuffleList(list1)"], "answer": "C. random.shuffle(list1)"}, {"question": "Suppose list1 is [4, 2, 2, 4, 5, 2, 1, 0], Which of the following is correct syntax for slicing operation?", "options": ["A. print(list1[0])", "B. print(list1[:2])", "C. print(list1[:-2])", "D.  all of the mentioned"], "answer": "D.  all of the mentioned"}, {"question": "Suppose list1 is [2, 33, 222, 14, 25], What is list1[-1]?", "options": ["A. Error", "B. None", "C. 25", "D. 2"], "answer": "C. 25"}, {"question": "Suppose list1 is [2, 33, 222, 14, 25], What is list1[:-1]?", "options": ["A. [2, 33, 222, 14]", "B. Error", "C. 25", "D. [25, 14, 222, 33, 2]"], "answer": "A. [2, 33, 222, 14]"}, {"question": "Suppose list1 is [1, 3, 2], What is list1 * 2?", "options": ["A. [2, 6, 4]", "B. [1, 3, 2, 1, 3]", "C. [1, 3, 2, 1, 3, 2]", "D. [1, 3, 2, 3, 2, 1]"], "answer": "C. [1, 3, 2, 1, 3, 2]"}, {"question": "Suppose list1 = [0.5 * x for x in range(0, 4)], list1 is:", "options": ["A. [0, 1, 2, 3]i", "B. [0, 1, 2, 3, 4]", "C. [0.0, 0.5, 1.0, 1.5]", "D.  [0.0, 0.5, 1.0, 1.5, 2.0]"], "answer": "C. [0.0, 0.5, 1.0, 1.5]"}, {"question": "what is the output print(1) ?", "options": ["A 1", "B 0", "C -1", "D 2"], "answer": "A 1"}]
